internetsourcebook.com 2000-12-06

# MindBranch - Privacy Policy

| 

**Our Policy**  
MindBranch, the Web’s leading market-intelligence provider, is committed to helping you make informed purchasing decisions. Our dedication to protecting your privacy ensures your ability to use our site with confidence. Any personal information that we collect allows us to expeditiously process orders and to provide a personalized and more efficient shopping experience; this information will only be used to support your relationship with MindBranch.

**Providing Personal Information**  
When a visitor requests a MindBranch page, our Web servers automatically recognize the browser's domain name and IP address; our servers do not record e-mail addresses. This information is used in order to determine what site sections are most utilized by our visitors. This information is collected for statistical purposes only.

Upon purchasing products or signing up for our newsletter, The MindBranch Monitor, you will be asked to provide your name, e-mail address, and contact information. The processing of purchases will also require a mailing address and a credit-card number and expiration date. This allows us to process, fulfill, and, if necessary, track your order. Credit-card numbers are used only for payment processing and are not retained for other purposes.

Additionally, we request the e-mail and mailing addresses of those participating in our surveys.

MindBranch uses this information to better understand our users’ needs and to provide optimal customer service. This information may ultimately be used to help you complete a transaction, to communicate with you, and to personalize our Web site for you. We may, in the future, use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the Web site, new MindBranch services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable. If you’d rather not receive this information, you will be given the option to change your preferences on your My MindBranch page.

**Security**  
MindBranch.com uses cookies to store your basic preferences and contact information. This information is for internal MindBranch use only and will not be divulged to any other party. A cookie stores your basic identifying information for use the next time your browser accesses our site. At that time, the cookie is matched to more detailed information that is securely stored on our servers. For your protection, credit-card information is not stored in your user profile. To change your browser’s cookie settings, explore the browser’s security options.

MindBranch is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure and to ensure data accuracy and the appropriate use of information, we utilize a proven security certificate service to protect such sensitive data as credit-card information and to ensure that all financial transactions are encrypted. 

**Our Pledge**  
MindBranch, Inc.,maintains a strict "no-spam" policy. MindBranch will not sell, trade, rent, or lease your personal information to others. We may choose to do so in the future with trustworthy third parties, but you can instruct us not to by sending an e-mail to [policies@mindbranch.com](mailto:policies@mindbranch.com). MindBranch may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information. MindBranch may disclose user information when we believe, in good faith, that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with the law, enforce or apply the terms of our user agreements, or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of MindBranch, our users, or others. 

**Access Your Information**  
Helping you maintain accurate personal-identification information is important to us. To update or review your user profile, which contains information related to your MindBranch account, simply access your My MindBranch page. 

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by MindBranch. Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this page.

We welcome your questions and comments about our privacy policy. Please send them to [policies@mindbranch.com](mailto:policies@mindbranch.com)

|   
---|---|---
